声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：66 亚历9大 wolfRay susan
校对：小帝 美景时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何   ==========
-你们这帮人在干什么? -我们在射击
What are you guys doing? we're shooting things.
这是去神庙的地图  那是个避难所
This is a map to the temple. it's a sanctuary.
这可能是岛上最后的安全地点
It may be the last safe place on this island.
如果你们现在就走  一天半就能到
If you leave now, you can get there in a day and a half.
你母亲会保护你的
Your mother will protect you.
Karl?  不要!
Karl? no!
-快走快走  他已经死了 -不要不要!
Come on. come on. he's gone. no! no!
等等!  不要!  我是Ben的女儿
Wait! wait! don't! I'm ben's daughter!
我是他的女儿!
I'm his daughter!
你有吃那个的处方吗?
You got a prescription for that?
有啊
Yeah.
我自己开的
I wrote it myself.
你看起来很糟
You look terrible.
谢谢
Well, thanks.
那些是什么?
What are those?
抗生素  我只是...
Antibiotics. I just got a...
胃里有虫
A stomach bug.
你应该吃点饼干
You should eat some crackers.
饼干总能让我好受些
Crackers always make me feel better.
他们怎么还没从船上回来  Jack?
Why aren't they back from the boat yet, jack?
Sayid说引擎熄火了
Well, sayid said the engine was down.
我猜他们是正在修理
My guess is they're trying to fix it
也在思考他们怎么联系不上我们
And wondering why the hell they can't get in touch with us.
-那你不担心吗? -不
And you're not worried? no.
我的肚子说我们要离开这个岛了
My gut says we're getting off this island.
你的肚子不是病了吗
I thought your gut was sick.
救人啊!  我需要帮助!
Help! I need some help! help!
Help! I need help!
我这里需要帮助!
I need some help down here!
狗一直在叫  我都没看到他
The dog was barking. I didn't see him.
抓住他了  拖他上来
I got him. flip.
你认识他?
Do you know who this is?
他是我们船上的
He was on our boat.
他是医生
He's the doctor.
我们都要挂了
We're all gonna die.
冷静点  胆小鬼
Calm down, chicken little.
天还塌不下来
The sky ain't falling just yet.
这就是他想要的  让我们内斗
This is exactly what he wants-- to fight amongst ourselves.
-你会犯错的  兄弟 -让他错吧  Hugo
You're making a big mistake, dude. it's his to make, hugo.
继续
Let's get on with it.
我要攻击西伯利亚
I'm attackin' siberia.
承让承让
Sorry.
不可思议  你就这样把澳洲给他了
Can't believe you're just giving him australia.
-澳洲是整个游戏的关键 -你说的
Australia's the key to the whole game. says you.
停下  跪下
Stop here. on your knees.
跪下
Get on your knees.
把这玩意儿关掉
Hey. turn this thing off.
求求你
P-please.
他们那还有个婴儿
There's a baby with them.
千万别...
Just promise you won't...
把防护关掉
Turn the fence off.
好的  关了
Okay. it's off.
暗号14-J
Code 14-j.
是谁?
Who is it?
-暗号14-J -我想是打给Ben的
Code 14-j. I think it's for ben.
"暗号14-J"是什么?
What's "code 14-j"?
你从哪里听到的?
Where did you hear that?
电话响了  我接了
The phone rang. I picked it up.
一个声音不停地说  "暗号14-J"
A voice kept repeating, "code 14-j."
我们要去其它房子
We need to get to the other house.
那里更容易设防
It's easier to fortify,
我们也能占据树林里的有利地形
And we'll have better position on the tree lines.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
翻译：且歌且行 Susan 美景 帝释天
校对：Susan 时间轴：amber后期：梁良
你好
Hello.
不不不  等等
No, no, no, no. wait.
等等  我能解释  你们会说英语吗?
Wait. I can explain. d-do you speak english?
好的好的
Sure. sure.
好的
Ah. okay.
好
Okay. okay.
Okay.
这是...
This...
投降了!  投降了!
Surrender! surrender!
哦  你会说英语啊
Oh, so you do speak english.
驾!
Yah!
让我猜猜  "14-J"不是用来叫匹萨的吧
Let me guess. "14-j" ain't the code for the pizza boy.
是一个预警系统
It's an early warning system.
-预警什么? -有人碰到了
Warning for what? somebody tripped
我们安全系统的面板开关
The panic switch at our security fence.
那就是说我们有人被俘获了
That means one of my people's been captured.
你们刚刚吵了多久才
How long did you guys debate amongst yourselves
决定要不要问我电话怎么会响的?
Whether or not to ask me why the phone rang?
五分钟
Five minutes.
那已经足够我们想好对策了
Well, so much for our head start.
等等  如果我们要转移
Hold up. if we're hunkerin' down,
-我去把孩子们带来 -别担心  他们很安全
I gotta grab frenchie and the kids. don't bother. they're safe.
-我昨天就让Rousseau Alex和Karl他们走了  -去哪?
I sent rousseau, alex and karl away yesterday. away where?
随便了  Claire还在睡觉  我去叫醒她
Whatever. claire's still sleepin'. I'll grab her.
没时间了
There's no time.
我会抓紧时间的
I'll make time.
不管这里发上什么  你都要活下来
It's very important that you survive
这很重要  John
What's about to happen here, john.
-所以我需要你跟着我 -我干嘛这么做?
So I need you to stay close to me. and why would I do that?
因为那些人不会冒险伤害我的
Because the people that are coming won't risk hurting me.
你想活下来吗?  我是你最好的机会
You want to live? I'm your best chance.
他的喉咙被撕开了
His throat was slit.
知道什么吗?
Know anything about that?
我上次见到他的时候  他还很好
No. uh, he was fine when I last saw him.
是什么时候?
Which was when?
什么时候?
When?
"什么时候"是一个相对的期限
"when" is kind of a relative term.
我们什么也不知道
We don't know anything about this.
固定电话修得如何了?
Any luck fixing the sat-phone?
哦  抱歉
Uh, yeah. sorry, no.
Mike...干得很不错
The, uh, mike was... smashed pretty good.
可能是最好情形了
Best-case scenario,
不过只能发射Beeps和Boops的信号
We'd only be able to broadcast tone squelch--beeps and boops. well, yeah,
不过你还是可以发射信息  对吗?
But you could still use it as sort of a telegraph, right?
如果我有些铁金属
If I had some strips of ferrous metal,
还有个九伏的电池夹
Uh, a 9-volt battery clip
还有些...电线
And some... wiring.
-我们从飞机上弄下来好多东西 -很好
We got a bunch of stuff that we salvaged from the plane. great.
我带你去看看
I'll show you where it is.
Bernard  你有空吗?
Bernard, you got a second?
那些人
These people who are coming--
-你很怕他们  是吗? -是的
You're scared of 'em, aren't you? that's right, john. I am.
怎么了?
What's going on?
离窗户远点  Hugo
Get away from the window, hugo.
-那Sawyer回来时怎么进来? -他不会回来
How's sawyer gonna get back in? he's not.
今早你看到Claire离开房子了吗?
Hey. you see if claire left her house this morning?
怎么了?  你拿着那个干嘛?
What's going on? why do you have that?
进屋去等着
Just get back inside and wait until--
进屋去!
Get back inside! aah!
快进去!
Get inside!
Claire!
下午好  先生
Good afternoon, sir.
下午好  我要一个房间
Good afternoon. I'd like a room, please.
好的  先生  这是您第一次来突尼斯
Of course, sir. is this your first time in tunisia?
不是  我来这有一阵了
No, but it's been a while.
你的名字?
Your name?
事实上  我是这里的优先顾客
I'm actually a preferred guest.
是以Dean Moriarty的名字订的
It should be under "dean moriarty."
当然  Moriarty先生
Certainly, mr. moriarty.
还有什么需要帮忙的吗
May I help you with anything else?
嗯  今天是几号
Yes. um, today's date is...
-十月二十四号  -2005年?
October 24th, sir. 2005?
是的  先生  2005年
Yes, sir. 2005.
谢谢
Thank you.
...Sayid Jarrah...
...sayid jarrah...
我只是想让我的妻子入土安息
Please. I just want to bury my wife in peace.
我要你现在就告诉我发生了什么事
Right now I need you to tell me what's going on.
我认为用正式的说  就是"震撼行动"
I think the technical term is "shock and awe."
他们想要威吓我  让我投降
They're trying to frighten me into surrendering.
那他们为什么没有开枪了
Well, why did they stop shooting?
那是Claire的房子吗  Claire在那儿
Was that claire's house? claire was there.
Hugo  不要抱着孩子站窗户边
Hugo, get the baby away from the window.
把他抱到里屋去
Put him in the back room.
你说我得活下来  为什么
You said I need to survive this. why?
因为现在只有一个人能帮我们了
Because there's only one person that can help us now,
那就是Jacob  我们得一起去找他
And that's jacob, and we have to go to him together.
你怎么认为我能找到他
What makes you think I can find him?
我甚至都不知道他的住处
I-i don't even know where the cabin is.
我明白  但Hurley知道
I know, but hurley does.
Claire!
Claire
你没事吧
Are you okay?
Claire
Charlie?
没事  没事  Aaron在哪里  Aaron在哪里
Okay. okay. okay. where's aaron? where's aaron?
他跟我们在一起  好了  我们得走了
He's with us. it's okay. we're gonna move now.
我们走
Let's go.
把前门开了
Open the front door!
Hugo  不要那样
Hugo, you don't want to do that.
把该死的门打开
Open the damn door!
开门
Open the door!
他妈的开门啊
Open the damn door!
小心
Careful.
她没事吧
Is she all right?
她晕过去了  不过应该没事
She got her bell rung, but she's gonna be all right.
他们开始开枪了  为什么
They just started shooting. why?
为什么这些人要毫无目的地滥杀无辜
Why slaughter people without even telling us what they want?
他们只是用滥杀无辜来激怒你  James
Those people were murdered to make you angry, james.
这样你就更有可能陷入狂暴
So you'd be more likely to come storming in here
-然后把我扔向虎口  -这有什么不好的
And throw me to the wolves. yeah, what's wrong with that?
我听来是个不错的计划  你觉得呢
Sounds like a great plan to me. what do you say, on three?
如果我是你  我就不会
I wouldn't if I were you.
闭嘴
Shut up!
Miles?
谁放你出来的
Who the hell let you out?
给我这个的人
The people who gave me this.
他们想要谈谈
They want to talk.
你这个饕餮之徒  你跟踪我
You vultures, you followed me
到提特里克  来监视我?
to tikrit... to spy on me?!
你到这里来干什么
What are you doing here?
我来找出杀你妻子的凶手
I'm here to find the man who murdered your wife.
你怎么到这里来的?
How did you get here?
我穿过叙利亚的边界过来的
I came across the syrian border.
-这不是你想象中的那么难  -你是怎样逃离
It's really not as difficult as you might-- how did you get off the
那个岛的?
Island?
你的朋友Desmond有一艘船
Your friend desmond had a boat.
还记得吗  伊丽莎白号
Remember? "the elizabeth."
我沿着航线去了斐济
I followed a heading to fiji.
然后我租了一架飞机
Then I chartered a plane.
为什么是现在
Why now?
你还记得Charles Widmore这个名字  对吗
You remember the name charles widmore, don't you?
那个家伙  他要全世界的都
The man who tried to convince the world
认为你们的飞机沉入了海底?
That your plane was on the bottom of the ocean?
这和我还有Nadia有什么关系
What does it have to do with me? with nadia?
她的队伍中有一个人
There was a man at her procession.
名字叫Ishmael Bakir
He goes by the name of ishmael bakir.
他是widmore的人
He's one of widmore's men.
有人五天前在洛杉矶
Bakir was last seen five days ago
最后一次看到Bakir
In los angeles,
是一个交通摄像头拍到的
Caught by a traffic camera,
超速从La brea和Santa monica的街角冲出去
Speeding away from the corner of la brea and santa monica.
那里离Nadia被杀的地方只有三个街区之遥
That's three blocks from where nadia was killed.
这些人为什么要杀她
Why would these people want to murder her?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是他们已经把她杀了
But they did.
他们有多少人
How many of 'em are there?
可能是6个  我不太清楚
Maybe six. I'm not sure.
你意思是你不确定
The hell you mean, you ain't sure?
你跟他们乘同一条船来的  不是吗
You came over on the same boat with 'em, didn't ya?
他们告诉我他们只是保卫人员
They told me they were just security.
-保护什么  -保护他
Security for what? for him.
只要他们抓到他  就会押送他回到美国本土
Once they got him, to escort him back to the mainland.
好吧  Miles  听起来
Well, miles, sounds like
你不准备要你的3200万美金了
You're not gonna collect your $3.2 million.
拿走吧
Just take it.
我为什么会跟他们谈话
Why would I talk to them?
因为他们有人质
Because they have a hostage.
那他们严重失算了
Well, then they've badly miscalculated,
因为我的人
Cause every single one of my people
-都准备好为岛而亡了  -是你女儿
Is prepared to die in service to this island. it's your daughter!
喂
Hello?
是Benjamin Linus吗
Am I speaking to benjamin linus?
请讲
That's right.
我叫Martin Keamy
My name is martin keamy.
我是Charles Widmore的手下
I'm an employee of charles widmore.
-谁是Charles Widmore?  -先听下
Who's charles widmore? later.
我要你从东边的窗户向外看看
I'd like you to go look out your east window
这样我们就可以面谈了
So we can talk about this face-to-face.
左边
To the left.
看见我了吗
You see me?
是的  我看到了
Yeah, I see you.
好的  Linus先生  我的条件是
All right, mr. linus, these are my terms.
你走出前门
You're gonna step out the front door,
把手放在头上
Put your hands above your head,
对直朝我走过来
And you're gonna walk straight to me.
只要你在我手上  我保证
Once I have you in my custody, then I promise you
屋子里的其他人会毫发无伤
That no one else in that house will be harmed.
你我都知道  只要你抓住了我
You and I both know that once you have me,
你就会毫无顾忌地
There's nothing to stop you
在这岛上大开杀戒
From killing everybody else on this island.
你认为我是那样的人?
What kind of guy do you think I am?
Martin christopher keamy
Martin christopher keamy--
前美国海军陆战队的一级士官
Former first sergeant, united states marine corps,
服役于1996年到2001年
Served with distinction from 1996 to 2001,
但之后
But since then,
你工作于一些雇佣军集团
You've worked with a number of mercenary organizations,
特别是在乌干达
Specifically in uganda.
所以我完全清楚你的底细  Keamy先生
So I know exactly what kind of man you are, mr. keamy,
我们可以不用拘束于礼节
And we can dispense with the formalities.
好的  Ben  你说对了
Okay, ben. you got it.
跪下
Get down.
你现在就给我滚出来
Get your ass out here right now...
否则我就杀了你女儿
Or I'm gonna kill your daughter.
我倒是有个相反的提议
I'd like to present a counterproposal.
我听着
I'm listening.
你和你的同伙
You and your friends...
你转过身去
You turn around.
回到你的直升机那去
Walk back to your helicopter.
然后飞走  就当作自己从来没有来到这岛上
You fly away and forget you ever heard of this island.
和你老爸说拜拜吧
Tell your daddy good-bye.
爸
Dad...
他们是当真的
They're serious.
他们已经杀了karl和我妈了
They killed karl and my mother.
Alex...
一切都在掌握之中
I have this under control.
一定会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
求你了  爸爸
Please, daddy!
求你了  求你了
Please. Please.
给你10秒钟  Ben
You have ten seconds, Ben.
好吧  听着
Okay, listen.
九...
Nine...
她不是我女儿
She's not my daughter.
八...
Eight...
她还是个婴儿的时候
I stole her as a baby
我从一个疯女人把她那里偷过来的
from an insane woman.
她只不过我手中的一颗棋子  仅此而已
She's a pawn, nothing more.
对我来说  她什么都不是
She means nothing to me.
我是不会出去的
I'm not coming out of this house.
所以  要是你想杀了  尽管开枪好了--
So if you want to kill her, go ahead and do it--
他们走了
I don't see 'em.
他们把她的尸体留那里  人都消失在丛林了
They just left her body there and disappeared into the jungle.
他们一定还没走多远
They won't be gone for long.
再过20分钟天就要黑了
It's gonna be dark in about 20 minutes,
到时  他们还会再来抓他
And then they're gonna come for him.
我们把他交出去得了
Then let's just hand him over.
我想这些人根本就没打算让我们
I don't think these people have any intentions
活着离开这里  James
Of letting us walk of here alive, James,
不管我们怎么做
No matter what we do.
我还不想死呢
Well, I ain't got no intention of dyin'.
他篡改了规则
He changed the rules.
你说什么?  谁?
What? who?
什么规则?
What rules?
你知道  我是对的
You know I'm right.
我们最好把他交出去  保住自己
Our best chance here is to toss him out and fend for ourselves.
嘿  你去哪
Hey! Where you goin'?
把这该死的门打开!
Open this damn door!
打开啊!
Open up!
走
Walk.
你是谁  你为什么要跟踪我?
Who are you and why are you following me?
我叫Benjamin Linus
My name is Benjamin Linus.
我要你帮我给Widmore先生捎个口信
And I need you to take a message to Mr. Widmore for me.
什么口信?
And what message is that?
杀的好
That should do it.
等等
Wait.
你要去哪里?
Where do you think you're going?
该结束了  Sayid
We're finished here, Sayid.
转身走开  当作什么都没发生
Turn around and walk away.
继续你对她的哀悼  继续你的生活吧
Mourn your loss. get on with your life.
我已经没法生活了  被他们夺走了
I have no life. they took it from me.
回去吧  Sayid
Go home, sayid.
一旦让你的悲痛变成了愤怒
Once you let your grief become anger,
你就没法脱身了
It will never go away.
这是我的经验之谈
I speak from experience.
这是我的战斗  和你没关
This is my war. It's not yours.
过去的八年  我一直的苦苦寻觅
I spent the last eight years of my life
我深爱的那个女人
Searching for the woman I love.
我最终找了  并和她结了婚
I finally found her and I married her.
可昨天我却参加了她的葬礼
And I buried her yesterday.
所以别跟我说  这不是我的战斗
So don't tell me this is not my war.
Benjamin...
下个目标是谁?
Who's next?
我会联系你的
I'll be in touch.
把这该死的门打开!
Open the damn door!
狗娘养的  把我们扔这了
Son of a bitch just left us here.
把门打开  怎么了
Open the damn door! what's going on?
Claire?
你没事吧  宝贝
You all right, sweetheart?
没事  有点站不稳  毕竟  我还活着
yeah, a bit wobbly, but, uh, I'll live.
话不要说的太快
Well, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
请原谅  James
Excuse me, James.
原谅你?
Excuse you?
你在里面做什么了?
What were you doing in there?
好吧  你们听仔细了
Okay, listen to me very carefully.
我要你完全按照我的话去做
I need all of you to do exactly as I say.
一分钟后  我们得拼命地从这跑出去
In a minute, we have to run from this house as fast as we can.
在我下令后  我要你们
At that moment, when I give the order, I want you to head
直接往树林那边跑
Straight for the tree line.
你是说跑向那些持枪的家伙?
You mean towards the guys with guns?
不是  我们要尽可能的离他们远点
No, we want to be as far away from them as possible.
好了  跑出去  快点出去
Okay, outside. outside now!
你做什么了?!
What did you do?!
你把那东西召出来了?
Did you just call that thing?
折回去!
Fall back!
跑!  跑  快跑!
Go! go, go!
往树林那边跑  我会赶上去的
Head for the trees. I'll catch up with you.
嘿  你要去那?
Hey, where are you going?
我总得和我女儿告个别啊  John
I have to say good-bye to my daughter, John.
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
可能真有信号
Might actually have a signal.
你在发送什么?
What are you sending?
"医生..."
"what..."
"他..."
"happened...
"现在..."
"to...
怎么样了...?"
The... doctor?"
好吧  他们没确切地说医生怎么样了
Okay. they didn't exactly say what happened to the doctor,
但你们的朋友都没事
But your friends are fine,
直升机明早就会回来
And the helicopter's coming back in--in the morning.
还有?
Well?
他在说谎
He's lying.
那条信息说的是:"你在说什么?"
What the message said was, "what are you talking about?
医生他很好"
The doctor is fine."
你知道摩尔斯电码
You know morse code.
那是什么意思--
What does that mean--
"医生他很好"
"the doctor is fine"?
我不知道
I don't know.
你干嘛撒谎?
Why are you lying?
你为什么要说
Why did you say
直升机明早回来?
That the helicopters are coming back?
Jack
Jack.
你会不会...把我们带离这个岛?
Were you ever... gonna take us off this island?
不会
No.
-Jack  -不会
-Jack. -No.
你的宝贝直升机向那边飞走了
I think your chopper buddies ran that way,
想追就去吧
If you wanna catch up.
好吧  不过我现在--现在还会和你们呆在一起
Yeah, I think I'll stay with you guys for--for now.
你女儿的死我很难过
Sorry about your daughter.
谢谢你  John
Thank you, John.
别废话  你向我撒谎了
That being said, you lied to me.
你说你不知道那烟一样的怪物是什么
You told me you didn't know what the smoke monster was.
我们到了木屋后你可以问Jacob一切
You can ask Jacob all about it when we go to the cabin.
等等  "Jacob?"
Hang on. "Jacob"?
谁是Jacob?
Who the hell's Jacob?
他会告诉我们下来该怎么做  James
He's the man that's gonna tell us what to do next, James.
你知道吗?我受够了
You know what? I'm done with all this.
我一开始就不该跟你们这帮疯子一起
I never should have followed you wackos in the first place.
我要跟Claire和孩子一起回海岸去
I'm goin' back to the beach, and Claire and the kid
你没意见吧?
Are comin' with me. you good with that?
是  我赞成
Yeah, I'm good with that.
我和你走
I'm coming with you.
走吧  你也来  Hurley
Let's go. You, too, Hurley.
你疯了吗?
Have you lost your mind?
Hugo必须和我们一起
Hugo stays with us.
-决不  -等等  别把我扯进去啊
-Not a chance. -Wait. Leave me out of this.
不好意思  Hugo  我们需要你找到木屋
I'm sorry, Hugo. we need you to find the cabin.
他不会和你去任何地方的
He ain't goin' anywhere with you,
-你个疯狗  -停下!都把枪放下  我和Locke走
-You crazy son of a bitch. -Stop! put the guns down. I'll go with Locke.
-Hugo  -没事的  Sawyer
-Hugo. -It's okay, Sawyer.
拜托  放下枪
Please, put your gun down.
你也是
You, too.
你没必要这么做
You don't have to do this.
你们先回海滩  我迟早会赶上的
You guys go back to the beach. I'll catch up sooner or later.
你要是敢动他一根毫毛...
You harm so much as one hair on his curly head...
我就要你的命
I'll kill you.
好吧
Fair enough.
我们走  走吧  走
Let's go. Go. Move.
怎么走?
Which way?
谢谢
Thank you.
晚上好  先生  需要帮忙吗?
Good evening, Sir. May I help you?
是的  我来找住在4E的Kendrick夫妇
Oh, yes. I'm here to see Mr. and Mrs. Kendrick in 4e.
这么晚吗  先生?
At this hour, sir?
他们知道我来
They're expecting me.
你只管打电话确认好了
Feel free to call up.
不用了  先生  晚安  先生
No need, sir. Good night, sir.
Charles  醒醒
Wake up, Charles.
我想着你什么时候会出现
I wondered when you were gonna show up.
我看到你好像晒黑了些
I see you've been getting more sun.
伊拉克现在正是好时节
Iraq is lovely this time of year.
你什么时候开始和苏格兰威士忌共眠了?
When did you start sleeping with a bottle of scotch by the bed?
当噩梦开始时
When the nightmares started.
你来是要杀我的吗  Benjamin?
Have you come here to kill me, Benjamin?
我俩都知道我不会那么做
We both know I can't do that.
那你为什么来这?
Then why are you here?
我来  Charles
I'm here, Charles,
是因为你谋杀了我的女儿
Because you murdered my daughter.
别站在那  用你那双
Don't stand there, looking at me
可怕的眼睛盯着我
With those horrible eyes of yours
还把那个可怜女孩的死归因于我
And lay the blame for the death of that poor girl on me
我们都知道
When we both know very well
她根本不是我杀的  Benjamin
I didn't murder her at all, Benjamin.
是你
You did.
不  不是那样的
No, that's not true.
是的  Benjamin  是那样的
Yes, Benjamin, it is.
你想耗子一样在午夜潜进我的房子
You creep into my bedroom in the dead of night like a rat
厚颜无耻的想摆脱自己的罪名?
And have the audacity to pretend that you're the victim?
我知道你是谁  孩子...
I know who you are, boy...
你是什么样的人
What you are.
我知道你拥有的  你从我这里抢走的
I know that everything you have you took from me.
所以...我再问你一次
So... once again I ask you,
你为什么来这?
Why are you here?
我来  Charles
I'm here, Charles,
是告诉你我要杀了你女儿
To tell you that I'm going to kill your daughter.
她叫Penelope  是吗?
Penelope, is it?
她离去后...
And once she's gone...
当她死后...
Once she's dead...
你就会明白我现在的感受
Then you'll understand how I feel.
你就会希望你没有篡改规则
And you'll wish you hadn't changed the rules.
你不会找到她的
You'll never find her.
那个岛是我的  Benjamin
That island's mine, Benjamin.
它以前一直是  以后也会是
It always was. It will be again.
但你永远找不到它
But you'll never find it.
那我觉得我们俩都得开始寻找了
Then I suppose the hunt is on for both of us.
我觉得是
I suppose it is.
好好睡吧  Charles
Sleep tight, Charles.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====